This is
an
awesome treasure
hidden at the end of the sea,
and anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage, have the courage
that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now, for together we
found we look through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the conscious point's our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage!
We can't stop all our troubles,
forget the past Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there, no regrets!
Every tear that we've cried
only helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow?
Luffy, Eneru's been up there for a while.
He must have taken the Golden Bell by now.
No matter how hard you stretch your arms,
there's no way you can reach up there.
If he took it, I'm gonna take it back.
Give me the waiver!
Even Heaven's Gate was blown
away in the twinkling of an eye.
Angel Island, it's completely destroyed.
But what are we supposed to do?
And where do we go?
To Cloud End, and then down to the
Blue Sea, like Captain McKinley said.
It's our only choice. Hold on.
There's still a lot of people in the White
White Sea who haven't been evacuated yet.
The Milky Roads leading
there have been destroyed.
They're gone.
I don't know how we can bring
those ships down without them.
So, you're saying we just
leave those people to die?
We're all doomed.
The White White Sea is lost.
It's not here.
It's fading away.
So this is it.
Splendid!
At last, the Grand Belfry that was once the
pride of the legendary city of Shandora.
Now it's mine.
A prize befitting a god
of my power and glory.
The fabled Belle,
the one that heralded the start of
this land's 400-year-old conflict.
Watch out!
Something's falling towards
us again! Wait. Take cover!
A leaf?
What's it say cut down this beanstalk
and make sure it falls towards the west
But what'll happen if we do that?
I've accomplished all of my
objectives but one, so now...
It's time I destroyed this
pathetic land and the cumuloregalus
clouds it rests on and set
off for the endless birth.
I'm actually going to miss
toying with the Skypians' lives.
And I rule.
Damn him.
Do you see that?
This one's even bigger!
Maybe we should get out of here.
While there's still some place to get!
Say goodbye, Skypiea!
It's even bigger than his last one!
That bastard!
Now that he's got his grubby
hands on the golden bell,
he has no more use for Skypiea!
We can't let him get away with this!
Wait, we?
But weren't you gonna escape?
Yeah, well, I can't leave
now with what's at stake.
Besides, you want to ring
that golden bell, right?
I've gotta!
For old-timer!
But with your arm, you
can't drive the waiver.
If I left you here, you'd
keep trying to jump up,
so leave the driving to me
and I'll get you up there.
Listen.
You've got to promise that you'll get
us out of this mess in one piece, okay?
Yeah, you got it. And thanks.
We've only got one chance
to get this thing right
I just hope they got my
message and Understand
what we're attempting
to do Let me get this
straight they're gonna
jump to The ark from the
falling beanstalk you
got any better ideas well
that's crazy they can't
Be serious then I'll leave
it to you to climb up
there and stop luffy he
won't listen look I don't
care how crazy it sounds.
We have no choice.
We've got to let him do this
If we stay here, we're just gonna
get pushed down to the ruins below?
Run!
Get away from the beanstalk!
I'll take care of it.
All I need to do is cut the vine
down towards that ship right but
That maniac is about
to wipe this land away,
and there are only two people who can
reach him before he sets that thing off.
Zoro, wait!
Nami and Luffy, you better get ready.
It's far too late to change things now.
The minute you enter the survival
game, your fates were cast in stone.
Anything you do is futile.
Okay, he's going to be just fine.
Zoro buddy, you're the
only one who can do this.
It's up to you.
Eneru, I am so sick of you.
Oh, right!
He did it!
Zoro!
Insolent little worm.
He did it!
He did it and got zapped,
but he did it! Oh, no.
The vine
The vine's not falling but he cut
it what is that thing made out of it
looks like a plant but it's Solid
as a rock pathetic this is what you
outsiders get for butting in
whatever what are you doing Quiet we
Shandians are the descendants of
kalgara not that kid in the Straw Hat
If anyone is to ring that bell,
it should rightfully be us.
Don't listen to him, Robin.
He's too banged up to stop us.
Besides, Nami and Luffy
are counting on us.
Our only priority right now
is knocking that thing down.
Speaking of which, Zoro's already
cut through half of the stem.
It probably wouldn't take too much
to cut through the rest of it.
My awesome dance of the exploding
stars should do the trick.
After just one little hit, even a gentle
breeze will knock that thing over.
Once again, it's up to me.
The last line of defense
in our merry band.
Robin, leave all the
dangerous stuff to me!
You tend to our fallen comrades.
They look like an oak
leaf mochi cake. Forward!
About that bell.
Four hundred years ago,
an explorer from my world said
he stumbled upon a city of gold.
People laughed at him
and called him a liar,
but he has a descendant today
who still believes the stories.
and has spent years searching the Blue
Sea for any evidence of the City of Gold.
If that golden bell can be rung,
everyone will know the City of
Gold is in the sky and not a myth.
That's the reason Luffy's up there.
Now do you understand Exploding Star Noble
isn't it trying to vindicate
a man he never met?
He's had chances to escape but he's
stuck around to see this thing through.
That guy's nuts!
Barrel Exploding Star?
Usopp Rubberband of Doom?
Regular Exploding Star?
What?
What is the name of this
explorer's descendant?
Mont Blanc Cricket Why?
The name of his ancestor who came here
Please tell me, was it Noland?
How?
Wiper?
What's going on?
Why are you crying?
Is this a sign from you?
Or a miracle?
What is it, Great Warrior Kalgara?
Come, Nola.
We'll ring the bell again today so the
sound reaches the ends of the earth.
Let's send the sound you love to
say hello to our friend Noland.
What just did that?
Guess it doesn't matter because it
couldn't even budge that beanstalk.
Maybe one of my triple explosions
will do the trick. Hey!
Reject!
What the heck was that?!
Why this?!
That fool!
A reject dial.
Now fall, Giant Jack. Fall!
Guys, we've got to run away!
This is it!
Get on, Luffy!
Gun it! Go!
I should mention,
I've never revved this Waver's jet
dial up to maximum power before.
I was a little scared to
see how fast it would go.
I guess we're gonna find out now if it'll
be too strong for me to control, huh?
Go for it, Nami! Okay!
Hang on, Lucy! Bye-bye!
It's falling!
He's right.
What's going on up there?
Well, Nami, Luffy, good luck.
We're counting on you.
If we let this place be destroyed,
we'll never get to ring that bell
and Cricket will never hear it.
He helped us, so we gotta help him.
Ring that bell and ring it loud.
Jump to Anaru's ship and stop that guy.
Do it!
Everything's up to you
guys now, you got it?
Do it!
My, my.
Now, why can't you wait for the completion
of Rick like the rest of the insects?
Their impatience will be their undoing.
Very well, then.
That you should even
try to reach me now is
insulin far beyond the point of stupidity.
Now pay for your folly, ma-ma-ra-ga.
That creep!
He's trying to destroy
the base of the Beanstalk!
Do something, Nami! Like what?
We're going too fast
and we're too high up!
If this thing loses its foundation,
it'll crash before we get to the top!
We won't reach Enoru and
we'll fall to our death!
Upper yard's being pummeled!
This is the end!
Lightning may not harm you,
but your abilities are absolutely
useless if you can't reach Maxim.
Now fall and face destruction
with the rest of Skypiea.
Say goodbye, boy!
The upper yard is crumbling.
Luffy!
Nami!
You know, I think he's trying to make
sure you don't get near him again.
Too bad, he's mine.
He's destroying the cloud
cover over the road!
He plans to destroy the ground itself.
So is Zoro that bastard?
It won't work, Eneru.
This city will never fall to you.
Waiver!
This land of Shandora was home
to a proud race of warriors.
This ancient city preserves
and protects their memory.
What's more, their memory
protects this city.
That mighty power will never fall to
you, no matter how much forest you burn.
This land won't fall.
I can still hear the little
fools whining down below
The birth, of course.
It didn't fall.
Upper Yard is still standing.
Its power is unbelievable.
It must be.
The birth is so powerful.
What fools we've been!
It was never something to be fought over.
We've spilled so much blood.
And lost so many countless lives.
How could we be so blind?
For 400 years?
Wiper!
Get out of there!
The beanstalk's coming down!
Come on, this way!
Let's move it!
Move it!
Now go!
Go!
Straw hatch!
Here I come, Anaru!
Those fools never learn.
Give back the golden bell right now!
That's enough.
It's ready.
Now disappear along with this land.
Rick!
Thanks, for your help.
It won't be for nothing!
Lumi, wait!
The Ark's over there!
No!
Don't do it, please!
The air current and lightning
discharges in there could kill even you!
What do you think you can do
against this kind of power?
Man of rubber!
Tang SHOCK!
SHOCK!
FIREWORKS!
GOLDEN PEANY!
You, with your thunder and lightning!
We made it all the way to Sky Island,
and you had to come along
and ruin the weather,
you electrical freak!
What's with all the crazy lightning bolts?
I forgot.
That gold ball stuck in his
arm is a natural conductor.
Well then, I'll just drop it before
you can discharge the electricity.
Let everything be destroyed!
Captain McKinley, please stop it.
This is God's land.
It's pointless.
I don't care if it's pointless.
It's the only thing people can do when
they're caught between life and death.
Don't you see?
We've abandoned our
home and chosen to live.
We can't go back, nor can we go forward.
Praying is all that we can do.
The song of the island when our ears
hear that again the war will have ended.
I wonder are we all doomed maybe
if i'd had the courage to stand
up to Enaru My friends would
have been spared all this oh Sue
does God exist
if he does why
Doesn't he save us please if you do
exist you must protect those brave
Save people and keep them safe!
Please, give us a miracle!
Protect this land!
Lord God!
That mass of thunderclouds has vanished!
What could have happened?
Oh, yeah!
It's him, Luffy!
Now rig it, Straw Hat!
Light the fire of Shandora!
Go, Loopy! Go, Loopy!
Let me hear it, Straw Hat!
The song of the island!
You destroyed my Rick!
Insolent Blue Sea ape! You're next!
I'll ring you along with the bell!
Impudent fool!
Two hundred million volts!
Ramaru!
What the hell is that?
Ring the bell.
Is that what you said?
You must be one of those fools who
believes in the old legend that when
the bell rings it will mean the end of
the war between Skypiea and Shandora.
I am God!
I don't care how strong you are,
you're still just a Paramecia type.
You could never match the might of my
Lugia power, no matter how hard you try,
no matter what you might do.
That won't work on me!
And quit calling yourself God!
What kind of God destroys
everything and saves nothing? Fake!
Well done, Rubberman.
It was very agile of you.
You grabbed it before
you could be impaled.
Luffy!
But what will you do now?
You have nowhere to run.
The pull of the golden
ball on your arm will
draw you deeper and
deeper onto my trident.
And if you should let go,
you'll fall to your death below.
I admit I'm impressed
you made it this far.
But this is the end for you,
boy. And this land. Everything.
I can easily create another Rick.
It's the duty of every
citizen here on the island.
I'm so very sorry.
Will the Sky Islands really be destroyed?
So you prefer to fall, do you?
Luffy, no!
Nami!
Get out of the way!
Hurry!
What's this?
You should never mess with me, earlobes!
Now Gum-Gum!
Rocket!
Gum-Gum!
Are you going to try that
same old trick again?
I'll keep trying to the bell ring!
This time I'll skewer you, fool!
All day, my fool!
Too fast!
When you finally return, what will
you think when you see we're gone?
Hold on a little longer.
I'll let you know that we're still here.
Noland!
Light the fire of Shandora!
The war in the sky began 400 years ago.
I didn't think I'd live
to see this moment.
Yes, the Holy Land.
We'll sing once more.
Someday it will.
Six years ago, on the island of Jaya and
the Grand Line, I saw the City of Gold.
The City of Gold does exist!
Not one person in history has ever
disproven the existence of Sky Island.
I'm a romantic just like you!
Let it rain!
Hey, Pops!
Can you hear it?
The City of Gold is here!
For 400 years, The city of gold
Has been in the sky
Not just like the moon, you'll never
change as you climb into the night!
But your reflection wanes,
then you disappear fading so silently.
Stay as you are, don't lose your way,
let these words guide you.
Don't ever look back!
Don't give up on your dreams!
They're windless nights,
they come to you All again and again
Until you see the journey through?
You may not return.
I hope that you learn To put your
past behind And just keep moving on.